SVITLANA MOISEIENKO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



- Turkey GMT+3
- Luchi_web
- Portfolio
- svetlana.moiseienko.web@gmail.com
- in <u>LinkedIn</u>

SKILLS

- TypeScript/JavaScript
- Next.js, React
- Redux/RTK
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS
- · Webpack, Gulp
- Tailwind, Bootstrap
- Figma, Adobe Photoshop
- Rest API
- Design Patterns
- Commercetools
- Scrum, Kanban

EDUCATION

RS SCHOOL

JavaScript/Front-end 2023Q1 March 2023 - September 2023

LABA

Project management in IT May 2023 - July 2023

UDEMY

Fundamental JavaScript July 2022 - Aug 2022

WROCLAW BUSINESS ACADEMY

Specialisation: management GPA: 4.6

PROFILE

I am a Frontend developer with more than one year of experience. I have experience in web application development, currently specializing in Next.js, React, Redux/RTK, TypeScript technologies. I also have knowledge in design and SEO optimization of websites.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

August 2023 - September 2023

 Developed in Team eCommerse site with Commercetools advanced tool. Worked with SDK, libraries and testing

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Malevich

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

 Developed corporate websites in React to train and develop new employees in a "pass the game" format, in development team.

FRONT-ENT DEVELOPER | PART TIME

FotoDom

July 2022 - Aug 2022

 Designed and developed a small promotional website for the company using Bootstrap as a base.

INTERNSHIP

Pago HR

May 2022 - June 2022

• Developed a website for a charity and also managed social media.

LANGUAGES

- Russian native
- English B1
- Ukrainian native
- Polish B2